A perfect town. An unthinkable crime. Can there ever be justice?
The Cheshire Murders is a documentary film directed by David Heilbroner.
In the early-morning hours of July 23, 2007, in Cheshire, Conn., ex-convicts Steven Hayes and Joshua Komisarjevsky broke
into the family home of William Petit, his wife, Jennifer, and their daughters, Michaela, 11, and Hayley, 17.
Petit was beaten and tied to a pole in the basement.
The three women were bound in their bedrooms while the men ransacked the house.
The brutal ordeal continued throughout the morning, ending
with rape, arson and a horrific triple homicide.
On July 23, 2007, two home intruders entered the home of the Petit
family in Cheshire, Connecticut, United States.
The perpetrators, Linda Mai Lee (known as Steven Hayes at the time) and Joshua Andrew Komisarjevsky,  initially planned only to burgle the
house, but went on to murder Jennifer Hawke-Petit and her two daughters, 17-year-old Hayley Petit and 11-year-old Michaela Petit.
Their father, Dr.
William Petit, managed to escape despite sustaining severe injuries.
Upon entering the Petits' home, Komisarjevsky beat William with a baseball bat, and he and
Lee restrained him in the basement, along with Jennifer and her daughters.
Lee later kidnapped Jennifer and forced her to withdraw money at a bank.
After returning to the home, Lee raped her and strangled her to death.
Komisarjevsky raped 11-year-old Michaela.
The invaders then decided to burn down the house to destroy evidence.
The invaders tied Hayley and Michaela to their beds, doused them and the house with
gasoline, and set it on fire, leaving them to die of smoke inhalation.
The case garnered significant attention in Connecticut, with the Hartford Courant citing
it as "possibly the most widely publicized crime in the state's history".
The murders received national and international attention, and had a significant
impact on Connecticut's death penalty, ultimately delaying its abolition.
Lee and Komisarjevsky were convicted of the murders and sentenced to death.
Their sentences were vacated in August 2015, when the Connecticut Supreme Court ruled that the death penalty
was unconstitutional and retroactively commuted all death sentences to life imprisonment.
The tone is dark.